# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# TAUFAN SAMUDRA AKBAR



# **OBJECTIVE**

I've been a developer since 2019 and it's still going on. I always put my passion on my job, and that's why i became developer until now. I am a fast learner, adaptable person and have the determination to always expand my knowledge. All the challenges that I have been through, have made me even better.

# **PROFILE**

0838 73360540 Jln Manyar 1 E3 No.24 Sawangan Permai, Depok. 16519 taufan70@gmail.com https://taufansa.github.io/myweb/

## **EDUCATION**

Informatics Engineer Telkom University (2015 -2019)

Bachelor of Computer Science (GPA 2.91)

SMA 46 Jakarta (2012 - 2015)

## **EXPERIENCES**

PT Link Net Tbk, 2021 Software Developer (March 2021 - Present)

PT Mitracomm Ekasarana, 2020 Web Developer (Sept 2020 - March 2021)

PT Polychem Indonesia Tbk, 2019 Web Developer (Sept 2019 - Sept 2020)

#### SKILLS

#### **Back End**

- PHP
- Java Spring

#### Front End

- VueJS
- Quasar Framerwork
- Jquery
- Bootstrap
- HTML + CSS

# Database

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Microsoft SQL Server

#### **Tools**

- GIT
- Postman
- Insomnia
- Intellij
- VS Code
- Sublime
- Navicat
- SQLYog